<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="amazon_class">
        Amazons are female warriors; they may be seen as the female equivalents of Barbarians,
        but rely more on skill and grace than on brute strength.
    </string>
    <string name="barbarian_class">
        Barbarians are savage warriors from uncivilized lands - or regarded as such by members of
        the dominant Greek-like culture. In the fantasy world of Mythika, most Barbarian
        player-characters come from the nothern wild lands of Hyperborea. In other universes,
        they may include Celts, Goths, Cimbrians and, of course, Cimmerians.\n
        \n
        Barbarians are born fighters, whose ferocity in battle largely makes up for their lack of
        military discipline.
    </string>
    <string name="centaur_class">
        Centaurs are the famous men-horses of legend, well-known for their recklessness and fiery
        temper. Centaur player-characters are assumed to belong to the nobler (or less beastly)
        breeds of their race.
    </string>
    <string name="noble_class">
        Nobles are the members of the ruling families of kingdoms and city-states. They are often
        seen as proud and haughty (some Noble families even claim to descend from deities!) but also
        tend to show a very strong sense of duty to their people and nation.
    </string>
    <string name="spearman_class">
        The Spearman (or hoplite) is an elite soldier who relies on his training and discipline on
        the battlefield. His favorite weapons are the spear and the shield.
    </string>
    
    <!-- Magician Classes -->
    <string name="elementalist_class">
        Elementalists are magician who draw their powers from the four classical elements defined by
        Greek philosophers: fire, water, earth, and air.
    </string>
    <string name="lyrist_class">
        Lyrists are wandering poets, musicians and storytellers with the Gift of Orpheus, which
        allows them to work magic through their mastery of the oratory  and musical arts.\n
        \n
        Their name comes from the lyre, their musical instrument as well as the symbol of their role
        as recipients of divine inspiration. All civilized people consider Lyrists to be as sacred
        as Priests.
    </string>
    <string name="nymph_class">
        Nymphs are nature spirits who act as protectors of forests, rivers, mountains, caverns, the
        ocean and other sanctuaries of Nature.\n
        \n
        The vast majority of Nymphs tends to be sedentary creatures but some of the younger ones
        sometimes leave their natural habitat to wander the world, out of sheer curiosity for
        mortals.
    </string>
    <string name="priest_class">
        Priests are devoted to the service and worship of a specific God or Goddess (chosen by the
        player or rolled randomly on Table 2B). Although most Priests live in temples or other
        sacred places, some of them are chosen by their god to lead a more adventurous life,
        going on quests, missions and expeditions.
    </string>
    <string name="sorcerer_class">
        Sorcerers are adepts of the magical arts who use their arcane powers to confuse and
        manipulate the minds, emotions and perceptions of other persons. Most Sorcerers are seen
        with mistrust and defiance by most people, even by other magicians. Mythic characters like
        Circe the Witch and Queen Medea are good examples of Sorceresses.
    </string>

    <!-- Magician Talents -->
    <string name="lyrist_talent">Orphic Voice</string>
    <string name="elementalist_talent">Elemental Mastery</string>
    <string name="nymph_talent">Odylic Charm</string>
    <string name="priest_talent">Spiritual Aura</string>
    <string name="sorcerer_talent">Psychic Gift</string>

    <!-- Specialist Classes -->
    <string name="hunter_class">
        Hunters are rural characters skilled in scouting, woodcraft and marksmanship.</string>
    <string name="thief_class">
        Thieves are cunning rogues who rely on luck, stealth and trickery to survive the
        vicissitudes of destiny and fortune.\n
        \n
        Despite what their name implies. Thieves are not necessarily treacherous or dishonest and
        can be as loyal companions of adventure as anyone else once you get to trust them. But
        getting to trust them is often the problem.
    </string>
</resources>